Guide to the Athletics and Recreation Department records, 1890-2009 RG0054
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Videotapes, Audiotapes, and Film, 1973-2003; RG0054 Series 38; 17.5 Linear feet (Box 11, Box 9, Box 10, Box 6, Box 7, Box 12, Box 4, Box 8, Box 5, Box 2, Box 1, Box 3, Box 13)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: GW vs. Maryland, Championship Game (VHS), 12/05/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 18)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: GW vs. Maryland (VHS), 2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 19)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: Michigan vs. Maryland (VHS), 2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 20)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament: Michigan vs. St. John's (VHS), 2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 21)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Arnold Communications, Sallie Mae, "Education New Legal" (60 sec.) and "Education New Legal Life" (30 sec.) (Digital Betacam), 11/08/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 22)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Howard, Merrell and Partners, "Large City" and "Business to Business" (Digital Betacam), 11/17/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 23)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, "Lobby Version with Rob Henninger Intro" (44:38), (VHS, 11/30/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 24)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, "Lobby Version with Rob Henninger Intro" (44:38), (VHS), 11/30/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 25)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, "December Madness" (05:03), (Betacam SP), 11/30/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 26)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Michigan vs. Maryland and St. John's vs. GW, (VHS), 12/02/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 27)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, St. John's vs. GW, (Betacam), 12/02/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 28)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Seton Hall vs. Illinois, Consolation Game (Betacam), 12/05/1999; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 18, Videocassette 29)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, St. John's vs. GW (Betacam), 12/02/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 1)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, St. John's vs. GW (VHS), 12/02/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 2)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, St. John's vs. GW (VHS), 12/02/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 3)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Michigan vs. Maryland, Tape 1 (Betacam), 12/02/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 4)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Michigan vs. Maryland, Tape 2 (Betacam), 12/02/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 5)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Army Fife and Drum Corps (VHS), 12/02/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 6)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, St. John's vs. Michigan, Tape 1 (Betacam), 12/03/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 7)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, St. John's vs. Michigan, Tape 2 (Betacam), 12/03/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 8)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Maryland vs. GW, Tape 3 (Betacam), 12/03/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 9)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Maryland vs. GW, Tape 4 (Betacam), 12/03/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 10)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, St. Johns/Michigan/Maryland/GWU Day 2 (VHS), 12/03/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 11)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Navy Ceremonial Drill Team (VHS), 12/03/2000; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 12)
  - GW NCAA (VHS), 02/15/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 13)
  - GWU Welcomes Basketball Coach Karl Hobbs (Betacam SP), 05/07/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 14)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, St. John's vs. GWU, Tape 2 (VHS), 08/21/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 15)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Maryland vs. GWU, Tape 3 (VHS), 08/21/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 16)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Maryland vs. GWU, Tape 4 (VHS), 08/21/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 17)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, St. John's vs. Michigan, Tape 1 (VHS), 08/21/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 18)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, St. John's vs. Michigan, Tape 2 (VHS), 08/21/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 19)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Maryland vs. Michigan, Tape 1 (VHS), 08/21/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 20)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Maryland vs. Michigan, Tape 2 (VHS), 08/21/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 21)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Loop tape with Rob Henninger Intro (89:06), (VHS), 08/24/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 22)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Loop tape with Rob Henninger Intro (89:06), (VHS), 08/24/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 23)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Promos, (Betacam SP), 10/31/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 24)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, NCAA Final Four 2002, (Betacam SP), 11/05/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 25)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Highlight Special, Non-Broadcast Loop Tape, (VHS), 11/19/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 27)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Highlight Special, Non-Broadcast Loop Tape, (Betacam SP), 11/19/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 28)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Maryland vs. Princeton, (VHS), 12/02/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 29)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, University of Connecticut vs. GW, (VHS), 12/02/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 19, Videocassette 30)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, GW vs. DePaul, Tape 1 (Betacam), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 1)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, GW vs. Stanford, Tape 2 (Betacam), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 2)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, GW vs. Stanford, Tape 1 (Betacam), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 3)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Maryland vs. GW, Tape 2 (Betacam), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 4)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Maryland vs. GW, Tape 1 (Betacam), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 5)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Maryland vs. GW, Tape 1 (Betacam), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 6)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Maryland vs. ND, Tape 2 (Betacam), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 7)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Game 1, Tape 2 (Betacam), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 8)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Game 1, Tape 1 (Betacam), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 9)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Game 2, Tape 1 (Betacam), 2002; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 10)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Game 2, Tape 2 (Betacam), 2002; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 11)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Highlights (VHS), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 12)
  - Astro Play (VHS), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 13)
  - GW NCAA (VHS), 12/21; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 14)
  - GW Sports Talk (VHS), 11/09; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 15)
  - GW NCAA (VHS), 03/15; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 16)
  - NCAA Sports Talk (VHS), 01/18; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 17)
  - GW Senior Package 2006, Comcast Sports Net (VHS), RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 18)
  - Washington Post Kidsfest (VHS), 01/15/2005; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 19)
  - Colonials Spot Mike Rogers (VHS), 2004-2005; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 20)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Promos (VHS), 2004; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 21)
  - Paramount Pictures Alfie, "Match/Marisa" (30 sec.) (Betacam SP), 10/22/2004; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 22)
  - Paramount Pictures Alfie, "Match/Marisa" (30 sec.) (VHS), 10/22/2004; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 23)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Flashbacks (VHS), 12/2004; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 24)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Gonzaga vs. Maryland (VHS), 12/06/2003; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 25)
  - West Virginia vs. Maryland (VHS), 12/07/2003; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 26)
  - GW Player Highlight (Betacam SP), 02/2004; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 27)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, University of Connecticut vs. Maryland, Championship Game (VHS), 12/03/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 28)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, University of Connecticut vs. Maryland, Championship Game (VHS), 12/03/2001; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 20, Videocassette 29)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, GW vs. DePaul, Tape 2 (Betacam), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 1)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Maryland vs. DePaul, Tape 1 (Betacam), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 2)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Maryland vs. DePaul, Tape 2 (Betacam), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 3)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Maryland vs. Illinois (VHS), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 4)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, St. John's/Michigan/Maryland/GWU, Day 2 (VHS), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 5)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Billboard and Halftime Stats Features (VHS), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 6)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Highlight Special, Broadcast Version (59:30), (VHS), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 7)
    General
    Includes Commercial Spots and Black Holes for Local Spots
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, (VHS), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 8)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, "Tickets" (Betacam SP), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 9)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Rob Henninger Intro and "BB&T Is" (4:41), (Betacam SP), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 10)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Rob Henninger Intro and "BB&T Is" (4:41), (Betacam SP), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 11)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Rob Henninger Intro and "BB&T Is" (4:41), (VHS), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 12)
  - BB&T Classic Basketball Tournament, Rob Henninger Intro and "BB&T Is" (4:41), (VHS), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 13)
  - Karl Hobbs Report for GW Jumbotron, (VHS), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 14)
  - Safeway/GW Promo, (VHS), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 15)
  - Sports Talk, (VHS), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 16)
  - United States Navy Seals, (30 sec), (Betacam), undated; RG0054 Series 38 (Box 21, Videocassette 17)
  - Josh Maurer Demo Tape (Audiocassette), 2003 (Box 21, Cassette 1)
- Athletic uniforms and memorabilia, ca.1990-2000; RG0054 Series 39; 1.0 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of a baseball uniform and hat, and a "GW Colonials" basketball towel. The materials range in date from ca.1990-2000.
  - Baseball uniform top, 1990 ca. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Baseball uniform top, blue with "GW" and "11" in gold lettering.
  - Baseball hat, 2000 ca. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Baseball hat, blue with "GW" in gold lettering.
  - Towel and patch, 1990 ca. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Small yellow towel with basketball and "GW Colonials" in blue lettering; Atlantic 10 Conference patch.
- Basketball game programs and media guides, 1959-2001; RG0054 Series 40; 1 Linear foot (Box 2, Box 1)
  This series consists of basketball media guides, programs, yearbooks of men's and women's teams, from sports information office.
  The materials range in date from 1962-1998.
  - GW vs. St. Johns, 01/10/1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Men's basketball game program
  - GW vs. Georgetown, 01/17/1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - GW vs. West Virginia, 01/26/1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - GW vs. V.P.I., 02/16/1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Men's basketball game program. V.P.I. now known as Virginia Tech.
  - GW vs. Maryland, 12/03/1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Men's basketball game program.
  - GW vs. Wake Forest, 12/16/1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GW vs. William and Mary, 12/14/1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Cincinnati vs. GW, 11/30/1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - All-American Holiday Doubleheader, GW vs. Mississippi State, 12/28/1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - GW vs. Virginia Tech, 12/30/1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - GW vs. West Virginia, 01/11/1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Maryland vs. GW, 12/03/1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Wiliam and Mary vs. GW, 12/08/1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Furman vs. GW, 12/14/1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Georgetown vs. GW, 01/13/1965 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - West Virginia vs. GW, 02/01/1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Davidson vs. GW, 02/05/1965 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - GW vs. Virginia Tech, 02/06/1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - GW vs. Virginia Tech, 02/18/1966 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Cincinnati vs. GW, 12/01/1966 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Citadel vs. GW, 12/10/1966 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Georgetown vs. GW, 12/14/1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - GW vs. Richmond, 01/28/1967 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - GW vs. Virginia Tech, 02/06/1967 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Maryland vs. GW, 02/09/1967 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Baltimore vs. GW, 12/01/1969 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Maryland vs. GW, 12/03/1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - V.M.I. vs. GW, 12/06/1969 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - William and Mary vs. GW, 12/30/1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Virgin Islands vs. GW, 01/22/1970 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - West Virginia vs. GW, 01/31/1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Penn State vs. GW, 02/07/1970 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - American vs. GW, 02/12/1970 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Virginia vs. GW, 02/17/1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Davidson vs. GW, 02/21/1970 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Baltimore vs. GW, 12/01/1970 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - GW vs. The Citadel, 12/17/1970 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Presidential Classic, GW vs. Richmond, 12/29/1970-12/30/1970 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - GW vs. Brown, 01/02/1971 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - GW vs. Pittsburgh, 01/06/1971 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - GW vs. Navy, 02/03/1971 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - GW vs. Miami, 02/11/1971 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - GW vs. Army, 02/12/1972 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - GW vs. Rochester, 02/17/1972 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - GW vs. East Carolina, 02/22/1972 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Tiawan National Team vs. GW, 11/06/1982 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - GW vs. Yugoslavia, 11/12/1983 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - GW vs. Marathon Oil, 11/10/1984 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Colonials Courtside, 02/21/1996-02/29/1996 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    Program for women's games vs. Xavier Feb. 21 and Virginia Tech Feb. 27, 1996; men's games vs. Duquesne Feb. 21 and Rhode Island Feb. 29, 1996.
  - Men's basketball media guide, NCAA tournament, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Men's basketball media guide, post season NIT tournament, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Men's basketball media guide, NCAA tournament, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Men's basketball media guide, NCAA tournament, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball programs and Colonial Illustrated, 12/03/1959-02/09/1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball programs, media guide, and Colonial Cager, 01/16/1986-12/12/1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball programs and Colonial Cager, 01/24/1988-12/01/1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Men's Basketball programs and Colonial Cager, 01/1989-12/22/1990 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball programs and Colonial Cager, 01/10/1991-12/11/1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Men's and Women's Basketball Colonial Courtside, and Men's Basketball program, 02/26/1995-12/11/1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Men's Basketball program, 11/15/2001 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Sports media guides, 1989-1998; RG0054 Series 41; 1 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of publications produced by the Athletics Communications Office, including sports media guides and programs. Sports include crew, women's gymnastics, and women's volleyball. The publications range in date from 1989 to 1998.
  - Cherry Blossom Invitational Crew Classic program, 04/15/1989 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Invitational Crew Classic program, 04/14/1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Invitational Crew Classic program, 04/13/1991 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - National Cherry Blossom Festival regatta program, 04/11/1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - National Cherry Blossom Festival regatta program, 04/03/1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Invitational Crew Classic program, 04/10/1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Crew Classic program, 04/13/1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Gymnastics program - Atlantic 10 conference championship, 03/22/1991 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Gymnastics program - Atlantic 10 conference championship, 03/26/1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Volleyball media guide, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Volleyball media guide, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Volleyball program - Atlantic 10 conference championship, 11/23/1991-11/24/1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Volleyball media guide, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Posters and Oversize Photographs, 1989-2007; RG0054 Series 42; 2.5 Linear feet (Box 5, Box 4, Box 6, Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
  This series consists of posters and oversize photographs of various sports teams, including men's and women's basketball, men's and women's crew, women's gymnastics, men's tennis, men's soccer, and football.
  The materials range in date from 1992-2005.
  - Basketball, gymnastics, crew posters, 1992-2005 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Posters from men's basketball (1992-95, 1999-2001, 2002-05, 4th and 8th annual BB&T tournament); women's basketball (1992-95, 1996-97, 1998-99, 2000-01, 2003-05, Elite 8); women's gymnastics (1994, 1997, ca.2000, 2005); men's and women's crew (ca.2000).
  - Atlantic 10 Conference Champions, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Colonials All-Century Men's Basketball Team, 2005 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Men's Basketball and Women's Volleyball photographs, 1950 ca.-2000 -- --ca. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Women's Gymnastics and Men's Soccer Posters, 2001-2007 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Inscribed poster of Iwo Jima, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Women's Basketball, Men's Tennis, and Women's Gymnastics Photographs, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Men's Basketball Photographs, 1950 ca. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Football photographs, 1940 ca. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Facsimile Military Recruitment Poster, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Basketball Championships Poster, Copy of Newspaper Article on Basketball, 01/15/1992-2002 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Men's Basketball enlarged newspaper articles, 01/26/1993-03/18/1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Oversize poster, Men's Basketball, undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - GW Athletics Timeline Poster, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Basketball programs and jerseys, 1962-2006; RG0054 Series 43; 2 Linear feet (Box 3, Box 2, Box 1)
  This series consists of basketball programs, photographs, basketball jerseys, a GW athletic blanket, trophies, and memorabilia. The materials range in date from 1962-2006 and were transfered to University Archives by the Athletics Department.
  - Basketball team photo, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Colonial basketball certificates, 2005-2006 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Vouchers for men's and women's games with the picture of the respective head coaches on a faux $5 bill.
  - Basketball game photos, 1971-1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Colonial Cager basketball program, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Men's game Jan. 9, 1990; women's games: Jan. 4, 6, 1990
  - Colonial Cager basketball program, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Men's and Women's games, Feb. 15, 17, 1990
  - Colonial Cager basketball program, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Men's and Women's game, Feb. 3, 1990
  - Basketball Program: President's Day Game, 02/17/1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    James Madison vs. GW, Feb. 17, 1992
  - Women's basketball program, 12/20/1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    GW vs. Vanderbilt, Dec. 20, 1993
  - GW basketball program, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Men's games, Jan. 6, 12, 1994; women's games, Jan. 12, 20, 22, 1994
  - GW basketball program, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Men's games, Jan. 29, Feb. 1, 1994; women's game Feb 3. 1994
  - GW basketball program, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Men's and women's game, Feb. 5, 1994
  - GW basketball program, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Men's games, Feb. 18, 21, 1994; women's games, Feb. 15, 17, 1994
  - GW basketball program, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Men's games, Feb. 24, 27, 1994; women's games, Feb. 26 Mar. 3, 1994
  - Colonials Courtside, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Basketball program for men's games Red Auerbach Classic; Dec. 2-3, 1994; women's games, Dec. 7 and GW Invitational, Dec. 9-10, 1994
  - Basketball - Atlantic 10 tournament press guide, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - GW baseball NCAA tournament guide, 05/31/2002-06/02/2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - GW baseball Atlantic 10 tournament guide, 05/16/2002-05/18/2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - GW football reunion, 04/28/2006-04/30/2006 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Photo of football game, 10/22/1967 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Color photo caption: Bruce Keith catches touchdown pass, GW 13 VMI 0
  - Audio tape, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Contains comments by Steve Bilsky (athletic director) and men's basketball coach Gerry Gimelstob
  - Ribbons, 1965 ca. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    5 gold with blue lettering ribbons: "GW Drill the Keydets", "Sack the Keydets VMI", "Chop the Shockers", "Trap the Mountainers", "Colonials Leash the Bulldogs."
  - Medal, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Small bronze medal of Southern Conference, founded 1921
  - Blanket, 1965 ca. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Buff and blue wool blanket, with "GW" letter
  - Basketball uniform, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Uniform (#21) and warmup set of Colleen McCrea, class of 1997.
  - Basketball jersey, 1995 ca. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Men's blue jersey top: "Colonials" lettering in white with yellow trim.
  - Trophy, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Southern Conference runner-up, basketball
  - Trophy, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Southern Conference, 1962, basketball player
- GW Spirit Program, circa 1980-2008; RG0054 Series 44; 4 artifact(s) 1 over-size textile box and 3 over-sized custom boxes.
  Arrangement
  Mascot heads are stored separately from rest of costume.
  Scope and Contents
  Includes 4 retired mascot costumes from GW Spirit Program:
  Costume 1: 1 plastic "George" head, 1 pair knee-breeches, 1 undershirt/waistcoat, and 1 blue dress coat with gold braiding and sequins.
  Costume 2: 1 plastic "George" head with ruffle, 1 white undershirt, 1 pair knee-breeches, 1 blue dress coat.
  Costume 3: 1 felt "George" head, 1 pair velvet knee-breeches, 1 white silk shirt, 1 purple waistcoat, and 1 gold dress coat.
  Costume 4: 1 cotton, blue sweatshirt; 1 pair cotton, blue sweatpants; and 1 pair cotton, blue shorts.
  - George costume 1: 1 pair knee-breeches, 1 undershirt/waistcoat, and 1 blue dress coat with gold braiding and sequins., circa 1980-2008; RG0054 Series 44 (Box 1, Object 1)
  - George costume 2: 1 white undershirt, 1 pair knee-breeches, 1 blue dress coat., circa 1980-2008; RG0054 Series 44 (Box 1, Object 2)
  - George costume 3: 1 pair velvet knee-breeches, 1 white silk shirt, 1 purple waistcoat, and 1 gold dress coat., circa 1980-2008; RG0054 Series 44 (Box 1, Object 3)
  - George costume 4: 1 cotton, blue sweatshirt; 1 pair cotton, blue sweatpants; and 1 pair cotton, blue shorts., circa 1980-2008; RG0054 Series 44 (Box 1, Object 4)
  - George mascot heads and tri-corner hat (belong to Acc 941 and costume 1), 1980-1990; RG0054 Series 44; 2 artifact(s) 1 oversize box (Box 2, Object 1, Object 2)
    Formerly ACC#941, formerly RG6.